本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： skywalker HTC 红鼻子的UFO 王老猫
校对： 小坏玩意儿   后期： 深影后期组
欧洲隧道终点站 法国加莱市
STTS19 能把服务隧道中点的灯打开吗
收到
- 看上去不像是事故 - 通知英国方面
她死在法国还是英国的边境
Is she on the French or the UK side?
她在国境线的正中间
她似乎不是欧洲隧道的员工
No, she doesn't seem to be Eurotunnel staff.
位于内部管理隧道
法国人派了一组犯罪现场调查员
The French are sending a crime unit.
英国警方也会参与
The British police will also attend.
- 是她吧 - 没错
怎么了 先生
Is there something wrong, sir?
你知道怎么了
You know what's wrong.
几乎要上公告栏了
It was practically in the staff bulletin.
疼吗
Did it hurt?
不 那个时候不疼
No, not at the time.
英国人来了
别担心 他们现在都会说法语
你们好
Bonjour.
- 你好 - 你好
- Bonjour. - Bonjour.
你们会说英语吗
- 我们的法医们已经开始工作了 - 好
- Our forensic teams are already working. - Sure.
她是被移尸到这的 看这姿势
She's been placed. The posture.
- 对 - 腿是在...
- Yes. - And the legs are...
头在法国 而且她是个法国人
Her head is in France and she's French,
所以这是属于法国的案件
so it remains a French investigation.
淡定 琼 我不是来吵架的
Steady on, Joan, I'm not looking for a war over it.
我不叫琼
My name is not Joan.
你是说受害人是法国人
Er, you said the victim's French?
昨天报道说有个国会议员失踪了 应该就是她
An MP was reported missing yesterday. We think it is her.
那你们认为尸体是怎么运到这的
And how do you think the body was brought here?
我们认为是一辆法国检修车运过来的
We're assuming it must be a French maintenance car.
其中一辆下落不明 司机也失踪了
One of them is unaccounted for and the driver is missing.
好吧 那咱们就等着
All right, well, we'll just wait
确认我们不用管辖...
for confirmation that we're not needed...
我可以确认
I can confirm that.
...听从一个英国长官 然后我们就走
...from a senior British officer, and then we'll be on our way.
我们站在远处 不会打扰的
We'll observe from a distance.
或许能得到一些线索
Maybe we can learn something, eh?
好
All right.
- 他们说什么 - 法国人会拿走尸体
- What did they say? - French have it.
咱们可以撤了
We can go and snuggle under our duvets.
法国人一点也不讲礼貌
No bloody manners, the French.
他们很直接 我很喜欢
They're direct. I quite like that.
我应该去告诉他们一些细节
I should go and give them my details.
该死
# 到我怀里来 #
Venez dans mes bras
# 靠近我 亲爱的 #
Closer to me, dear
# 让我自己 #
Donnez-vous à moi
# 抛开所有恐惧 #
Set aside all fear
# 一根红线 缠绕永远 #
Restons enlaces pour l'éternité
# 是的 你是我的 #
Yes, you shall be mine
# 直到地老天荒 #
Till the end of time
隧道谜案 第一季第一集
你好
Hello?
我是斯蒂芬・布芒特
This is Stephen Beaumont.
我是维拉妮卡・莫伦诺 我一直在等...
This is Veronica Moreno. I've been waiting...
我在法国出差
I had business in France.
我只是... 我们什么时候见面
I just... When can I see you?
一小时之内见
I'll meet you in an hour.
是你吗
是
一切都安排好了 我和飞行员说过了
他在办理前往巴哈马的出境许可证
好
你在哪儿
赶快回家吧
不行 太危险了
你让尼古拉斯把黄金卖了吗
是 他将把所有东西放在我名下
好
阿兰 亲爱的 告诉我发生了什么
告诉我你在哪儿
夏洛特
他们想要我的命
谁想要你的命
我会尽快打来
那些人想要出卖我们国家
让移民拥有比法国公民更多的权利
接受欧盟霸权
施舍别人
玛丽・维伦纽夫最后一次在公众露面
宣称对欧洲和移民要增加限制
不到二十四小时 她被绑架 挖空 抛尸
放置于欧洲隧道的中点
一辆检修车九时到达法国边界 十时十分离开
车辆下落不明
司机也是 他叫卢克・维希涅夫斯基
进入内部管理隧道需要通过指纹身份系统
- 用的是他注册的指纹 - 监控录像呢
只有入口有 但看不清楚
好
谁挖空了她
也许他有癖好
我不这样想
这样做很明智
易于运送并搬卸尸体
否则她的肠子会流出来
手法严密 谨慎 干净
步骤需要非常精确
一个有条不紊的杀手 至少我们知道了这个
不 这是个麻烦
嘿 亚当
Hey, Adam.
- 你抓到他们了吗 - 谁
- Did you catch them? - Who?
- 那些坏蛋 - 还没
- The bad guys. - Not yet.
还疼吗
Does it still hurt?
是的
Yeah.
你和亚当说了让他多帮些忙吗
Did you speak to Adam about helping out more?
他睡了
He's asleep.
抱歉 我没等你就开始了
想看一下吗
这案子很有趣
记住我教给你的
嘴唇和耳朵轻微发紫
多处点状出血
皮下有斑点
窒息而死
很好
死后被切成两半
去看看腿
肤色不同
有两个死者
她是英国人
或是威尔士人 这是威尔士国旗
这处褪色是什么
好样的
原以为你会忽略它
腿部被冷冻过
冻了多久
至少六个月
这是蓄谋已久的
你是慈善机构来的吗
Are you from the charity?
我朋友说你会帮我们
My friend said you would help us.
他们拒绝了你的庇护要求
They've denied your asylum claim?
我全家人都被杀了 凶手是...
My whole family, they were murdered by...
我不是上诉委员会
I'm not the appeal panel.
我只是想知道目前的状况
I'm just establishing the present situation.
我不能回哥伦比亚
I cannot go back to Colombia.
我们慈善机构有个宿舍 你可以待段时间
Our charity has a hostel where you can stay for a short time.
然后我们会考虑不同方案
Then we'll consider the options.
跟我来
Come with me.
给我十块钱 斯蒂芬
Suck you off for a tenner, Stephen!
坦妮娅...
Tania...
喝点汤去 别买海洛因
Soup, not smack.
被害人一
被害人二
你好
Yeah?
是卡尔・罗巴克吗
Am I speaking to Karl Roebuck?
是的
Yeah.
法国警察爱丽丝・瓦塞尔曼 咱们昨天见过
Elise Wassermann, French police, we met yesterday.
昨天
Yesterday?
不 我不喜欢果酱
No, I don't like marmalade.
笑什么
What is it?
我老婆在说梦话
My wife is talking in her sleep.
她刚刚说"我不喜欢果酱"
She just said, "I don't like marmalade."
她喜欢果酱吗
Does she like marmalade?
我觉得她喜欢
Well, I thought she did.
很奇怪
That's strange, then.
我想告诉你最新的情况
I wanted to update you.
那应该是你的案子吧
I thought this was your case now.
下半身是另外一个女人的
The lower half of the body belonged to another woman.
还是个英国人
We believe she was British.
为什么
Why?
一个纹身 上面有英国和威尔士国旗
A tattoo. With a Union Jack and the flag of Wales.
还写着"我爱你 妈妈"
And the words, "I love you, Mum."
所有你要查出有那样纹身的失踪威尔士女孩
So you need to check out missing Welsh girls with that tattoo.
好 一上班我就打给你
Right, I'll call you as soon as I'm on duty.
我需要有人马上能做这件事
Then I need the name of somebody who can do it now.
你考虑过从事外交工作吗
Have you ever considered a career in the diplomatic service?
没有
No.
如果有进一步的消息请尽快通知我
Please call me as soon as you have any information.
人真多
Plenty of 'em.
等等
Hold on.
吉玛・柯万
So, Gemma Kirwan.
混血
Mixed race.
格兰奇镇 卡迪夫市
Grangetown, Cardiff.
七个月前其母亲报警称其失踪
Reported missing by her mother seven months ago.
我找到了维伦纽夫的调查员 吉尔斯・里加
她生前见到的最后一个人
- 他在哪儿 - 马赛
他开会后去的那里 随后来警局接受传唤
我的新女友也来自马赛
- 你有女朋友了 - 是啊
我们上床的时候
她坚持要戴上手铐
我不喜欢这样 感觉跟上班一样
别告诉爱丽丝
- 她会想加入 - 没错
她会告你挪用警用资源
菲利普交了新女友
她来自马赛
需要正式命令你才能回家吗
英国人认为他们已确定第二具尸体的身份
他们想要DNA样本 罗巴克探长正在赶来
他不靠谱
现在是英法联合调查 我们别无选择
对他友善些
请确保您的手刹已拉起
Please ensure that your handbrake is on
并且档位在一档或停车档
and your vehicle is in first gear or park.
为了您的安全与舒适
For your safety and comfort,
我们建议您待在您的车中
we recommend that you stay with your vehicle.
不要在穿越过程中走出车辆
Do not stand or walk between the vehicles during the crossing.
我给你留了一些食品券和其他生活用品
I left some food vouchers and a few other bits to help you get by,
在我给你找到更长久的解决方案之前暂且如此
until I find a more permanent solution for you.
如果你想了解这个国家的民众心理
You should read this,
我该看看这个
if you want to know about the mentality of this country.
记录一下而已 我喜欢记住我帮助过的人
For my records. I like to remember the people I help.
那条路方向不对 咱不去那儿
That's the deviation. We're not going there.
方向不对
That's the deviation.
那是去汽车轮渡的路 咱不去那儿
That's going to the car ferry. We're not going there.
这条路是去...
This is going to...
汽车轮渡
the car ferry.
该死
Oh, bollocks!
这是到哪了
Where are we?
不好意思 抱歉
Pardon. Sorry.
是 是 是 抱歉
All right. Oui, oui, oui. Pardon.
打扰一下
瓦塞尔曼警长在哪
Uh... Capitaine Wassermann?
瓦塞尔曼警长 不在这层
去一层看看
你会说英语吗
这里是... 三楼
This is...third floor.
她在一楼
She is on first floor.
一楼
First floor. Okay. Oui.
- 你得下楼找她 - 好的 非常感谢
- You have to go down. - Down. Merci beaucoup.
来一个羊角面包吗?
Vous voulez un croissant?
- 不用 谢谢 - 不吃
- Non, merci. - No?
你在减肥吗
Are you on a diet?
- 不是 - 真的不吃 好吧
- No. - No? Good.
大家好
Bonjour.
近来如何
Comment allez-vous?
告诉我这个失踪女孩的个人情况
So, tell me about this missing girl.
吉玛・柯万 二十三岁
Gemma Kirwan, aged 23,
七个月前失踪于福克斯顿市
disappeared from Folkestone seven months ago.
我以为她是威尔士人
I thought she was Welsh.
人就是这样 不喜欢一直待在一个地方
That's the trouble with people. They won't stay in one place.
就她的职业来看 我们的数据库里
Given her profession, it's highly likely we've got her
很可能有她的DNA信息
DNA on our database.
就她的职业来看 当初你们警方也很可能
And given her profession, it's also likely
没怎么努力去找过她
not much effort was made to find her.
但她们行踪不定
Well, they're a transient bunch.
我想法国应该也有些失踪妓女
I imagine there's a few French prostitutes
没被仔细调查过
who haven't been searched for too carefully either.
- 是的 可能是的 - 是啊...
- Yes, that is probably correct. - Yes...
我还在术后恢复阶段
I'm recovering from an operation.
结扎手术
The snip.
什么
The what?
结扎手术
La vasectomie.
显然比生孩子还要痛
More painful than childbirth, apparently.
你有孩子吗
You got kids?
这个世界上的孩子够多了
There are enough kids in this world.
我有五个
I've got five.
但是分别由三任妻子生的
Three different mums, though.
那结扎也许是个好主意
A vasectomy was probably a good idea, then.
- 别动那个 - 这不是你 对吧
- Don't touch that! - It's not you, is it?
- 你怎么知道的 - 首先 她在笑
- How do you know? - She's smiling, for one thing.
其次 没有人会在办公桌上放自己照片
No one keeps a picture of themselves on their desk.
你们是双胞胎
You're a twin.
检修车找到了
- 在哪儿 - 终点站后面
- 司机呢 - 下落不明
这车不错
Nice car.
是的 我挺喜欢的
Yes, I like it.
很好
Good.
打扰一下
我想他把尸体的其他部分丢在了别的地方
I suppose we assume he's dumped the rest of the body elsewhere.
他在玩我们
He's taunting us.
我们拿到了维伦纽夫的通话记录
一个人打了许多次 叫夏洛特・鲁伯特
还有一条威胁短信"离我丈夫远点"
- 她是阿兰・鲁伯特的妻子 - 是的
他们住在布伦附近
我去一趟
回见
Oh, moi aussi.
在西班牙 成百上千的人们在游行
抗议政府的紧缩政策
需要打扫吗
好 谢谢
一位警方发言人说
抗议者态度强硬 寻求有力解决措施
欧洲人的梦想啊
很快就会爆发冲突了
暴乱什么也改变不了
总有人要为此买单
您还需要什么吗
- 你有手机吗 - 有
我的手机被偷了 需要打给我妻子
谁是阿兰・鲁伯特
Who is Alain Joubert?
是我们国家的著名金融家
One of our leading financiers...
也是上一任政府财政紧缩政策的顾问
and an adviser on austerity measures to the last government.
他不太受欢迎
He is not popular.
真的吗 怎么会
Really? How come?
他靠经济危机大赚了一笔
The crisis made him even richer.
我开玩笑的
I was joking.
是的 我知道
Yes, I got that.
你不太喜欢笑话 是不是
You're not really one for jokes, are you?
有时是 看这笑话好不好笑
Sometimes. It depends if they're funny.
英国人很注重幽默
The British place a lot of value on humour.
这有时会让你们因此忽视更重要的事
Sometimes it makes you lose sight of things that are more important.
这只是我的观点
That is just my opinion,
无意冒犯
I'm not trying to offend you.
没事 我知道
No, sure.
我以后会找机会和你谈谈
I'll bring you up to speed
我眼中法国人的缺点
with my assessment of French national defects later.
那我会洗耳恭听
I'd be interested to hear your views.
阿兰 是你吗
是
你知道加莱的战争纪念馆在哪儿吗
- 是的 - 去那里找我
好 我会去的
- 现在就来 - 好 我马上出发
- 鲁伯特夫人 - 我是
我是刑侦大队的爱丽丝・瓦塞尔曼
这是英国警察卡尔・罗巴克
好
什么事
关于玛丽・维伦纽夫 你给她发了条威胁短信
她起诉我了吗
你会讲英语吗
抱歉 我的法语不太好
Sorry, my French is very poor.
但我还是在努力学
I'm working on it, though.
你觉得玛丽・维伦纽夫和你丈夫之间
Did you think there was something going on
有发生过什么事吗
between Marie Villeneuve and your husband?
不 她在演讲中抨击了他
No. No, she was attacking him in her speeches.
听着我现在真的没有时间
我们能下次再谈吗
Can't we... this wait until another time?
恐怕不行 请进屋吧
I insist. Please go inside.
你知道玛丽・维伦纽夫失踪了吗
Are you aware that Marie Villeneuve is missing?
不知道
No.
现在真的不行 请让我走吧
Please, I can't do this now. Please, let me go.
请坐下
Sit down, please.
听着 我必须去见我丈夫 他压力很大
Listen. I have to go and see my husband. He's very stressed.
很可能会自杀 拜托了
He might be suicidal. Please.
坐下 鲁伯特女士
听着 你这个不可理喻的人
你认为你可以闯入这里对我发号施令
坐下 鲁伯特女士
求你了
Please.
我保证会去找你们谈的
I promise I will come and talk to you.
真的没什么
This is nothing.
我和玛丽上学时就认识了
I knew Marie from school.
她把我丈夫当成政治皮球 利用了他
She started using my husband as a political football,
所以我打电话给她让她停止这一切
so I called her to ask her to stop.
她没接 我才给她发了短信 拜托了
I texted, because she wouldn't answer. Please.
我保证会带着律师去警局见你们的
I promise I will come and report to the police station with a lawyer.
塞西尔 我一会儿给你回电话
什么
等一下 我听不见
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
我保证会在车上给我的律师打电话的
I promise I will call my lawyer from the car.
请一定要打 否则我会有麻烦的
Please do, or I'll be in trouble.
没准已经有麻烦了
I may be already.
让奥利弗去协调
你让她走了
You let her go.
是的
Er, yeah.
我不明白你为什么这么做
I don't understand why you would do that.
我想这不是主要问题
No, I think that's part of the problem.
我才是首席探员
I am the lead investigator.
听着
Now, listen.
那个女人非常焦虑 担心他的丈夫...
That woman was acutely distressed, frightened for her husband...
这是谋杀调查
This is a murder investigation.
但她并不知道 而且她的解释也完全合理
But she didn't know that. And her explanation was entirely plausible.
你也许觉得我有些讨厌
You might find my manner a little annoying,
太多笑话 讲话随意 诸如此类...
too many random jokes, conversations, whatever...
我没说过我讨厌
I didn't say I found it annoying.
但是我当警察已经很久了
But I have been a policeman for quite a long time,
而且我觉得干的还不错
and I like to think a good one,
我知道什么时候询问别人是不适宜的
and I know when it's an inappropriate time to question someone
什么时候可以适当灵活些
and when it's time to show a little flexibility.
战争纪念馆 1939-1945
我很想你
这是黄金的文书
飞行许可通过了 我们明天就可以离开
谢谢
我自己走
为什么
你不能离开我 我什么时候跟你会合
我不能把你牵涉进来
但是我已经被牵涉进来了
我是你妻子
你是我拥有的一切
这正是你想要的
都结束了 Charlotte
我不再爱你了
已经很久了
我做了一切你要我做的
是的
这不公平
照顾好自己
爱丽丝 你要我怎么做
失踪的司机已经不是嫌疑人了
我们不知道凶手是英国人还是法国人
- 我不能跟英国人说 - 他放走了个证人
好吧 这个决定不合常规
但夏洛特・鲁伯特遵守了承诺
她的律师说她会来的
这跟她没关系
你要知道不是所有人都和你的做法一样
依法办事是必须的
那是指
等等我
Wait for me!
和你的法国同仁怎么样
How's it all going with your French counterpart?
还不错...
Yeah...
很多法式作风 低调又性感
Lots of Gallic style? Understated, yet sexy?
爱丽丝
Elise?
开花耳朵 很胖
Cauliflower ears. Very fat.
法国英雄
就像奥贝里克斯
Looks a bit like Obelix.
我就当是了 别伸出你的魔爪哦 坏家伙
I'll take that as a yes! Paws off, buster!
说真的 她像被灌了魔法药水
Seriously, she fell in the magic potion,
非但没给她力量 还夺走了她所有的社交能力
but instead of giving her strength, it took away all her social skills.
对亚当来说我不是个好父亲
I was a bad dad to Adam.
你不是一个坏父亲 你只是没在他身边
You weren't a bad dad, you just weren't there.
- 爸爸 - 爸爸
- Daddy! - Daddy!
嗨 我想搭个便车顺便帮你指路
Hi, thought I'd hitch a ride and give you directions.
我有导航仪
I have a sat nav.
很现代化嘛
Ah, très moderne!
我更青睐地图
I prefer maps.
记住 我们在左侧行驶
Remember, we drive on the left.
我们找到了检修车司机
We've found the maintenance driver.
被海水冲到了沙滩上
Washed up on a beach.
好吧
Okay.
- 你还在不高兴吗 - 不
- You still sulking? - No.
我还在生气
I'm still angry.
- 想掰手腕一决胜负吗 - 不想
- Want an arm wrestle? - No.
长官命令我必须和你一起工作
I've been told I have to work with you.
好的
Okay.
那我们开始工作吧
Let's go to work, then.
你在发推特吗
You on Twitter or something?
- 怎么了 - 你在写什么
- So? - What are you writing?
"我的天啊 猜猜我刚才跟谁睡了 大笑"
"OMG, guess who I just fucked? LOL."
是的 我还说你狂妄自大 老二很小
Yeah. I also said you had a massive ego and a tiny cock.
前者倒是真的 后者就有些刻薄了
Well, the first's true. The second's a bit harsh.
也许小于平均值 但是 谁在乎呢
Smaller than average, maybe, but, who cares,
还是有大把漂亮的蠢女孩愿意舔它们
if I can still get stupid, pretty girls to let me come in their mouths?
你真的可以吗 没发现
Did you really? I never noticed.
再说 我跟着你是为了毒品
I was only after you for your drugs, anyway.
好吧 如果你愿意 可以在出去时舔舔包装纸
All right, well, you can lick the wrap on the way out if you like.
不 你不能改变那该死的截稿时间
No, you can't change the fucking deadline.
那告诉那些侏儒们别修改我的文章
Then tell the pygmies not to change my copy.
这是篇精打细磨的辩论文 不是什么意见表
It's a finely-honed polemic, not a suggestion sheet.
怪就怪这个时代吧 老朋友
Blame the times, old son.
莱维森报告 自我管理 品位风化等等
Post-Leveson, self-regulation, taste and decency, blah-blah-blah.
是啊 是啊 听着 总之
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Listen, anyway,
我五点交 好吗
it's going to be with you by five, all right?
很好 我能问问这篇精打细磨辩论文的内容吗
Lovely. Can I ask what's in the latest finely-honed polemic?
英国著名演员
斯蒂芬・弗雷 希腊自杀率和同志婚姻
Uh, Stephen Fry, the Greek suicide rate and erm...gay marriage.
非常好 我让侏儒们待命
Spiffing. I'll have the pygmies put on stand-by.
喂
Yep?
丹尼・希勒
Danny Hillier?
你是谁
Who's this?
如果你想要个真实的故事 你应该问问警察
If you want a real story, you should ask the police
在欧洲隧道发生了什么
what is happening in the Eurotunnel.
为什么你不直接告诉我呢
Why don't you tell me what's happening in the Eurotunnel?
你是个记者 丹尼
You're supposed to be a journalist, Danny.
但我会给你个线索
But I'll give you a clue.
他们找到了一半国会议员一半妓女
They've found half an MP and half a prostitute.
是啊 很好笑 某人
Yeah, very funny, Jonno.
听着 我说过 五点的时候给你 好吗
Listen, as I said, it'll be with you by five, all right?
这之中有一个女孩是吉玛・柯万
One of these girls is Gemma Kirwan?
是啊
Yeah.
右边那个
That one, on the right.
查克斯正在查询车牌号
Chuks is running traces on the registration plates.
头儿 我们找到匹配的了
Boss, we've got a match.
尸体被扔到隧道入口的那天
The owner of a mobile phone which was used in Calais,
加莱市一部手机曾在附近使用过
near the tunnel entrance on the day the bodies were left there.
太不小心了吧
Too careless, huh?
是谁
Who is it?
丹尼・希勒 小报记者 住在桑盖特
Danny Hillier. Tabloid journalist. Lives in Sandgate.
丹尼・希勒
Danny Hillier.
他在我们的报纸之一上写意见栏
He writes an opinion column in one of our newspapers.
偏执出租
Bigotry for hire.
有些他说的事情是关于钱的 也挺有趣的
Some of what he says is actually on the money. Quite funny, too.
特别是英国幽默 我想你会欣赏的
It's an especially British humour I think you'll enjoy.
怎么了
What?
你的车闻起来像只湿狗
Your car smells like wet dog.
哈 我没有狗
Ha! I haven't got a dog.
不好意思 给我 不要乱动备案系统
Sorry. Here, don't mess with the filing system.
你的家也这样吗
Is your house like this?
我的妻子是个室内设计师
My wife's an interior designer.
说真的 她很成功
Seriously, she's very successful.
这车是我躲避风格独裁的唯一避难所
This car is my only refuge from the tyranny of style.
你用德国方式拼写你的名字
You spell your name the German way.
是啊 纪念卡尔・马克思
Yeah. After Karl Marx.
我父亲是忠实共产主义者 这里还是煤田时
My dad was a die-hard Communist. He was a miner in the coalfields,
他是一名矿工
when there used to be coalfields round here.
你当警察是为了气他吗
Did you join the police just to annoy him?
不是故意的
Not consciously.
查克斯 怎么了
Chuks. What's up?
什么
What?
好的 我们快到了
Right, we're nearly there.
探长卡尔・罗巴克
DCI Karl Roebuck.
法国警察爱丽丝・瓦塞尔曼
Elise Wassermann from the French police.
我们知道车里的那家伙 情况怎么样
We know the guy in the car. What's the situation?
我们在跟他通话 现在没多少时间了
We've got him on the line. There's not much time left.
这车被镭射引爆器密封了
The car is sealed with laser triggers.
我要跟他讲话
I need to speak to him.
丹尼 我是爱丽丝・瓦塞尔曼 法国警察
Danny, this is Elise Wassermann, French Police.
丹尼 你找过妓女吗
Do you use prostitutes, Danny?
什么 这是什么变态的笑话吗
What? Is this some kind of sick fucking joke?
七个月前 在福克斯通红灯区
Seven months ago, your car was picked up on CCTV
你的车被监控摄像头拍下来了
in the red light district of Folkestone.
你觉得现在是说这件事的时候吗
You think now is a good time to bring it up?
这可能会帮到我们
It might help us.
我不需要妓女 也从没在福克斯通勾搭过女人
I don't need to use prostitutes, and I've never Kerb crawler in Folkestone.
如果你想深入调查 我还有张违规停车罚单
I might have a parking ticket if you want to look into that though.
你把车借给过其他人吗
Did you lend your car to anybody?
没有 你赶快把我弄出去啊
No! Look, just get me the fuck out of here!
- 你最近去过加莱吗 - 没有
- Have you been in Calais recently? - No.
你知道你的手机为什么会在加莱使用过吗
Can you think why your mobile was used in Calais?
我的手机 它丢了 或在酒吧被偷了
My mobile, it was lost, or stolen in a bar.
他们为什么不尽全力把我弄出去
Look, why aren't they doing anything to get me out?
他们什么都没做
They are not doing anything!
他很害怕 可能会引爆炸弹
He's panicking, he might detonate the bomb.
快他妈把我搞出去 从窗户上想想办法
Get me the fuck out of here! Do something with the windows!
丹尼 我是刑事调查局的卡尔・罗巴克
Danny, this is Karl Roebuck, CID. I'm right here.
好的 跟我讲话  丹尼
All right, talk to me, Danny,
让专业人士集中注意把你救出来
let the experts concentrate on getting you out of there.
是啊 他们是错误的存在
Yeah, there's only one thing wrong with that picture.
这些专家赶快把我弄出去啊
These fucking experts are doing fuck all to get me out!
问他在哪儿丢的手机
Ask him where he lost his mobile.
他们完全是废物
They're completely useless!
你有家人吗 丹尼
You got family, Danny?
没有 我父母都去世了 只有个兄弟
No, my parents are dead. I've got a brother.
- 我们的关系不是很好 - 真遗憾
- We don't really get on. - That's a shame.
问他有没有人最近用过他的车
Ask him if anybody else has used his car recently.
我有兄弟姐妹 我们也不常见面
I've got a brother and sister, I don't see too much of them either.
- 我们没时间了 - 电话给我
- We're out of time. - Give me the phone!
他们要去哪 他们要去哪 不 不 不
Where are they going? Where are they going? No, no, no!
等等 你们不能把我留在这儿 求求你 回来
Wait, you can't just leave me! Please! Come back!
回来啊
Come back!
丹尼 如果炸弹爆炸了
Danny? If the bomb goes off,
你感觉不到疼痛 也不知道发生了什么
you won't feel any pain or know anything about it.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为你的大脑没有时间
Because your brain won't have time
去接收你身体传来的消息
to register the messages sent from your body.
一切都会结束的
It will just end.
难道你不相信上帝吗
Don't you believe in God?
不信 你呢
No. Do you?
我不知道 有时候我会
I don't know. Sometimes I do.
这一切都是毫无意义的吗
How could it all be pointless?
重点是要抓住那个对你做这件事的人
The point is to catch the person who did this to you.
你是在哪儿丢的手机
Where did you lose your mobile?
我告诉过你 一个酒吧
I told you. In a bar.
哪个酒吧
Which bar?
所有人 趴下
Everybody, down!
我毁了我自己
I've soiled myself.
上帝啊 谁来帮帮我
Oh, God! Someone, help me!
我想我现在得到了你全部的注意
So, I assume I now have your full attention.
这只是开始
毫无疑问 你会问 为什么
You will be asking, of course, why?
谁会这么做 要传达什么信息
Who would do such a thing? What is the message?
你们不会失望的
真相快大白了
我们会离真相越来越近的
We shall all be getting closer to the truth.